<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:image="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/image/" version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General News</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/</link><description>General News</description><atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.aninews.in/rss/feed/category/national/general-news.xml"></atom:link><language>en-us</language><category>General News</category><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 09:43:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Uttarakhand: 5.0 Earthquake strikes Pithoragarh</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/uttarakhand-50-earthquake-strikes-pithoragarh201811111509470002/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/earthquake_nov11.jpg" alt="Reprsentative Image" title="Reprsentative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pithoragarh (Uttarakhand) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): An earthquake measuring 5.0 on the Richter scale struck Pithoragarh district of Uttarakhand on Sunday afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;The earthquake occurred at 12:37 pm and the epicenter was 10 km below the surface, mainly affecting the Nepal and Uttarakhand border region.&lt;br /&gt;No loss of life or damage to property has been reported. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/uttarakhand-50-earthquake-strikes-pithoragarh201811111509470002/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/earthquake_nov11.jpg</url><title>Uttarakhand: 5.0 Earthquake strikes Pithoragarh</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/earthquake_nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>India sits on volcano of unemployment after demonetisation, GST: Chidambaram</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/india-sits-on-volcano-of-unemployment-after-demonetisation-gst-chidambaram201811111509470001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg" alt="P Chidambaram" title="P Chidambaram"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indore (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Analysing the current situation of the Indian economy, former Finance Minister and senior Congress leader P Chidambaram here on Sunday underlined that ever since demonetisation and the Goods and Services Tax (GST) were rolled out by the Bharatiya Janata Party-led central government, jobs are a 'scarce' even for college pass-outs making India sit on a volcano of unemployment.&lt;br /&gt;"Jobs were destroyed due to demonetisation and GST. New jobs are scarce even for college-educated youth. Many unemployed people have given up seeking employment because the situation is hopeless. I am afraid we are sitting on a volcano. Growing unemployment is a volcano that can erupt at any time. The government that promised to create two crore jobs a year is utterly clueless. The overall economic situation of the country is quite fragile. There is no sign of recovery," Chidambaram told media here.&lt;br /&gt;Talking about GST, Chidambaram said: "After the UPA rolled out VAT smoothly in 2014-15, the next logical step was GST. GST was and is a good idea. Unfortunately, the BJP blocked the GST legislation for nearly six years. When the BJP came to power it embraced the idea of GST. However, the GST that it introduced was not the same that was known all over the world. Its BJP's own distorted version."&lt;br /&gt;He underscored, "Everything about the present GST is wrong - the design, classification of goods and services, multiple rates, high rate of tax, dual control by the centre and states, multiple registrations, multiple returns, inefficient GST network, insufficient capacity, absence of provision to file the revised returns, etc. In my view, the next government in the Centre must completely redesign GST and reintroduce a true GST regime that will promote the growth of trade, business and exports."&lt;br /&gt;Emphasising that the GST and demonetisation are the two prominent causes of economic stress, Chidambaram said: "Both were self inflicted moves. The country suffers while the rulers rejoice in making grand promises, renaming cities, capturing crucial institutions, intimidating critics and the media and unleashing a vendetta against all opposition parties," he said. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/india-sits-on-volcano-of-unemployment-after-demonetisation-gst-chidambaram201811111509470001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg</url><title>India sits on volcano of unemployment after demonetisation, GST: Chidambaram</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Police arrest mining baron Janardhan Reddy in bribery case</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/police-arrest-mining-baron-janardhan-reddy-in-bribery-case201811111424540001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Reddy_Nov11.jpg" alt="Janardhan Reddy" title="Janardhan Reddy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bengaluru (Karnataka) [India], Nov 11 (ANI):  Former BJP minister and Bellary's mining baron Gali Janardhan Reddy was arrested on Sunday in an alleged bribery case, involving Ambident Group. He is suspected to have received 57 kg gold worth Rs 18 crore to help an accused in a case being investigated by the Enforcement Directorate (ED).&lt;br /&gt;His arrest comes a day after Reddy appeared before the investigating agency after his anticipatory bail was rejected by the court. Police said he was interrogated till late night on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;"We have taken the decision to arrest him on the basis of credible evidence and witnesses' statements. We will produce him before the magistrate. We are going to recover the money and give it to the investors," said Alok Kumar, Additional CP, Crime Branch, Bengaluru Police.&lt;br /&gt;Earlier, Bengaluru Commissioner of Police T Suneel Kumar had stated, "A company Ambident, set up in 2016-17 assured investors a return of 30-40 per cent per month in the form of profits. Thousands of people were lured to invest. Initially, they returned the first installment of profits as promised following which more people poured in."&lt;br /&gt;"Subsequently, when the company failed to return the principal amount, cases were registered. In January 2017, the ED raided the company. The crime branch took over the case and a probe was conducted which revealed that transactions to the tune of Rs 18 crore were carried out," Kumar had added.&lt;br /&gt;Later, it was discovered that the company had allegedly transferred the money to Ramesh Kothari who runs a billion business in the name of Ambika Jewellers. On quizzing Kothari, he informed that he had used the money to buy the gold, which was handed over to Reddy's personal assistant Ali. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/police-arrest-mining-baron-janardhan-reddy-in-bribery-case201811111424540001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Reddy_Nov11.jpg</url><title>Police arrest mining baron Janardhan Reddy in bribery case</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Reddy_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>BJP desperately eyeing RBI reserves after demonetisation catastrophe: Chidambaram</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-desperately-eyeing-rbi-reserves-after-demonetisation-catastrophe-chidambaram201811111415380001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg" alt="P Chidambaram" title="P Chidambaram"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indore (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Former Finance Minister and senior Congress leader P Chidambaram on Sunday launched a scathing attack on the Bharatiya Janata Party-led central government for desperately "eyeing" the reserves of the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) after having "failed" to get money out of demonetisation.&lt;br /&gt;Chidambaram said, "After having failed to get money out of demonetisation, the BJP-led Centre is now eying the reserves of the RBI which is why they have started this problem with the RBI after four-and-a-half years of being in power."&lt;br /&gt;His statement comes in the wake of reports stating that with the RBI's surplus reserve running up to Rs 9.63 lakh crore, the Centre is now planning to ask the bank to fix the norm on surplus reserve.&lt;br /&gt;"Demonetisation was the beginning of the problem. After 'Notebandi', the Finance Minister (Arun Jaitley) said that out of the 15 lakh 44 thousand crore rupees, something like three to four lakh crore will not come back to the Reserve Bank of India and that will be transferred to the Government of India. The Attorney General of India, Mukul Rohatgi told the Supreme Court - and I was present there - that their calculation shows that the government will get a windfall of three to four lakh crore rupees. They got zero. 99.3 per cent of the currency notes came back to the RBI," Chidambaram told media here.&lt;br /&gt;"The government thought they could make a profit, but they got nothing. Today, they are desperate for money. Why? GST collections are short of the target, net direct tax collection is short of the target, the fiscal deficit of 3.3 will not be met. Therefore, they are desperate for money to meet the fiscal deficit target. They also want money because this is the election year and they have always spent. They don't have the money," he added.&lt;br /&gt;"In four-and-a-half years, this was not a problem, earlier they didn't want the reserves. Today when they have effectively got four months before (Lok Sabha) elections, they are eyeing reserves of the RBI," he said.&lt;br /&gt;Chidambaram said that demonetisation is an "ill-conceived decision that derailed the economy."&lt;br /&gt;"In the immediate aftermath of demonetisation, millions of jobs were lost, millions of people were forced to borrow, thousands of MSMEs were shut down, and over a hundred people died while standing in queues. Later, the GDP growth slowed down to 8.2 per cent in 2015-16 to 6.7 per cent in 2017-18. By any account, demonetisation was a catastrophe. In my view, it was an ingenious officially blessed money laundering exercise," Chidambaram said. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-desperately-eyeing-rbi-reserves-after-demonetisation-catastrophe-chidambaram201811111415380001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg</url><title>BJP desperately eyeing RBI reserves after demonetisation catastrophe: Chidambaram</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Chidambaram_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>AP CM Naidu inducts two new ministers</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/ap-cm-naidu-inducts-two-new-ministers201811111349300001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naidu_Nov6.jpg" alt="Chandrababu Naidu" title="Chandrababu Naidu"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amaravati (Telangana) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister N Chandrababu Naidu on Sunday inducted two new ministers in his Cabinet, eight months after the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) decided to severe ties with the TDP after the regional outfit pulled out of the National Democratic Alliance (NDA) in March this year.&lt;br /&gt;The two ministers who were inducted in N Chandrababu Naidu-led government are NMD Farooq, who was the chairman of Andhra Pradesh Legislative Council and Kidari Sravan Kumar, son of late MLA Kidari Sarveswara Rao, who was shot by Maoists in September this year. Sravan Kumar is a novice in politics. He holds a Bachelor of Technology degree from the Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Varanasi.&lt;br /&gt;The newly-inducted ministers were administered the oath of office and secrecy at the Raj Bhawan by Andhra Pradesh Governor ESL Narasimhan. The ministers will be given the portfolios earlier held by BJP MLAs Pydikondala Manikyala Rao, who was Endowments Minister and Kamineni Srinivas, who was the Health Minister. They had resigned from the Cabinet on March 8 following the rift between the Telugu Desam Party and the BJP. Andhra Pradesh will go to polls in May next year. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/ap-cm-naidu-inducts-two-new-ministers201811111349300001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naidu_Nov6.jpg</url><title>AP CM Naidu inducts two new ministers</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naidu_Nov6.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Kanker IED blast: BSF personnel succumbs to injuries</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/kanker-ied-blast-bsf-personnel-succumbs-to-injuries201811111344180001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/accident08.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kanker (Chhattisgarh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): A Border Security Force (BSF) personnel, who was injured in an Improvised Explosive Device (IED) blast in Kanker's Koyalibeda area of Chhattisgarh this morning, succumbed to injuries.&lt;br /&gt;Sub-Inspector (SI) Mahender Singh had sustained splinter and bullet injuries on his neck. A native of Dumariya village of Bharatpur district in Rajasthan, Singh belonged to 35th Batallion of the BSF.&lt;br /&gt;A set of six IEDs were planted in a series and were set off in one go between village Gome and Gattakal in Koyalibeda.&lt;br /&gt;The IED blast comes a day ahead of the assembly elections in Chhattisgarh. As many as 18 constituencies in eight Maoist-affected districts -- Bastar, Kanker, Sukma, Bijapur, Dantewada, Narayanpur, Kondagaon and Rajnandgaon will go to polls tomorrow. The polling for remaining 72 seats will take place on November 20 and the counting of votes will take place on December 11.&lt;br /&gt;Tight security arrangements have already been put in place in the Naxal-affected areas of the state to ensure that no untoward incident occurs during the polling process. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/kanker-ied-blast-bsf-personnel-succumbs-to-injuries201811111344180001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/accident08.jpg</url><title>Kanker IED blast: BSF personnel succumbs to injuries</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/accident08.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>BJP to reach out to MP voters through street plays</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-to-reach-out-to-mp-voters-through-street-plays201811111317290001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Bhopal_nov10.jpg" alt="Visual from Bhopal, MP" title="Visual from Bhopal, MP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhopal (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): At the time when social media platforms are being used to reach out to voters, the Bharatiya Janata Party in Madhya Pradesh has decided to bank on street plays to woo the voters in the ensuing Assembly polls in the state. Through street plays, the BJP will apprise the people in small towns and rural areas about developmental works carried out by Chief Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan led government in the state.&lt;br /&gt;BJP leaders on Sunday gathered at the party office here and shortlisted several drama groups for their upcoming campaigns. Scores of artists residing across the state had come for the audition test. Those selected were asked to perform street plays on the themes pertaining to the BJP government's achievements in the state.&lt;br /&gt;Speaking to ANI, Bablu Jha, an artist said that his group is all charged up for the election campaign for the BJP and added that they will make all efforts to "persuade people to press the button having lotus symbol on the electronic voting machines on the election day."&lt;br /&gt;Elections to the Madhya Pradesh Legislative Assembly will be held on 28 November to elect 230 members. The result will be declared on December 11.(ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-to-reach-out-to-mp-voters-through-street-plays201811111317290001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Bhopal_nov10.jpg</url><title>BJP to reach out to MP voters through street plays</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Bhopal_nov10.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Name changing an attempt to demolish idea of India: Mehbooba</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/name-changing-an-attempt-to-demolish-idea-of-india-mehbooba201811111250320001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Mufti_Nov11.jpg" alt="Mehbooba Mufti" title="Mehbooba Mufti"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar (Jammu and Kashmir) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Former Jammu and Kashmir Chief Minister Mehbooba Mufti has hit out at the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) for changing the names of cities and towns and said that the move was an attempt to demolish the idea of India.&lt;br /&gt;"Name changing is an attempt to demolish the idea of India we grew up with. It is an assault on the country's composite Ganga-Jamuni culture. BJP is trying to tell the Muslims that they don't belong to this place. But be sure it is as much my country as yours. We are just not going anywhere," Mufti tweeted on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;Mufti reacted on the micro-blogging site to Suheldev Bharatiya Samaj Party (SBSP) chief and Uttar Pradesh Minister Om Prakash Rajbhar's statement where he asked the BJP to change the names of three of their Muslim leaders-Shahnawaz Hussain, Abbas Naqvi, Mohsin Raza - before changing the names of different towns and places in the state.&lt;br /&gt;There is a sudden spurt in demands seeking change in the names of various cities after Uttar Pradesh Chief Minister Yogi Adityanath renamed Faizabad as Ayodhya and Allahabad as Prayagraj. Recently the name of Mughalsarai Railway Station was renamed as Pandit Deendayal Upadhyay Junction. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/name-changing-an-attempt-to-demolish-idea-of-india-mehbooba201811111250320001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Mufti_Nov11.jpg</url><title>Name changing an attempt to demolish idea of India: Mehbooba</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Mufti_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>BJP failed to develop Chhattisgarh even after 15 years' of rule: Congress</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-failed-to-develop-chhattisgarh-even-after-15-years-of-rule-congress201811111240220001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Sharma_Nov11.jpg" alt="Anand Sharma" title="Anand Sharma"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Delhi [India], Nov 11 (AN): Congress leader Anand Sharma on Sunday took a jibe at Chief Minister Raman Singh-led Chhattisgarh government stating that the state remained underdeveloped even after 15 years of Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) rule. The state goes to polls tomorrow.&lt;br /&gt;Sharma told ANI, "It has been 15 years that the BJP is in power in Chhattisgarh, but still the state is not counted in the list of developed regions of India.  In terms of health infrastructure, Chhattisgarh is placed at the 21st position while in education it does not even make it in the top 15 places. If one looks at the unemployment rate, currently more than 25 lakhs of youths are without jobs."&lt;br /&gt;He cornered the ruling NDA government at the Centre as well as the state government over the chief minister's son's name figuring in the Panama papers. "Why is the Prime Minister silent on the name of Raman Singh's son appearing in Panama Scam? Why is Raman Singh silent on this?" he questioned.&lt;br /&gt;Touching upon alleged chit fund scam in the state, the Congress leader said that scores of people have been looted. "There is Chit fund scam in Chhattisgarh. Why no action has been taken on the scam?" he said.&lt;br /&gt;Expressing anguish at the state government's performance, Sharma said: "Around 50 per cent of Chhattisgarh population is below the poverty line. Why wasn't the state developed even after it is so rich in the natural resources. Corruption and mining mafia have flourished in the state," he stated&lt;br /&gt;As many as 18 assembly seats in eight districts of Chhattisgarh will go to polls tomorrow. The polling for remaining 72 seats will take place on November 20 and the counting of votes will take place on December 11.&lt;br /&gt;Tight security arrangements are in place in the Naxal-affected areas of the state to ensure that no untoward incident occurs during the polling process. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/bjp-failed-to-develop-chhattisgarh-even-after-15-years-of-rule-congress201811111240220001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Sharma_Nov11.jpg</url><title>BJP failed to develop Chhattisgarh even after 15 years' of rule: Congress</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Sharma_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>MP BJP MLA equates Congress with 'butchers' for promising gaushala</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/mp-bjp-mla-equates-congress-with-butchers-for-promising-gaushala201811111225010001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Rameshwar_Sharma11.jpg" alt="Rameshwar Sharma" title="Rameshwar Sharma"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhopal (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Taking a dig at the Congress party for promising 'Gaushalas' in every Gram Panchayat in their manifesto for Madhya Pradesh assembly elections, Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) MLA Rameshwar Sharma has said the "butchers" are dreaming about cows just for the sake of votes.&lt;br /&gt;"Now butchers are dreaming about cows just for sake of votes. It is the height of hypocrisy that the Congress workers kill a cow on camera in Kerala, but in Madhya Pradesh the Congress pretend to be cow worshippers," Sharma told ANI.&lt;br /&gt;Yesterday, the Congress promised 'Gaushalas,' 'Ram Path' and Narmada Parikrama Path and a spiritual centre to woo voters to its fold in Madhya Pradesh which goes to polls on November 28.&lt;br /&gt;The 'gaushala' or cow shelter will be set up in all village Panchayats, which will be funded by the state government. The manifesto also promises to ban alcohol in the state.&lt;br /&gt;In an attempt to outsmart the BJP, the Congress manifesto known as 'Vachan Patra' or 'Sheet of promises,' focuses on, among other things, the issues which have not only been close to its rival BJP's heart, but have also been giving political sustenance to the saffron outfit for long.&lt;br /&gt;From having a special 'Parikrama path' around river Narmada to the construction of 'Ram path', the Congress has touched upon almost everything to appease Hindu voters. A special Spiritual Department will also be set up if the Congress is voted to power in the state, which has 230-member Assembly. The counting of votes will be done on December 11, 2018.&lt;br /&gt;The Congress has promised special provisions for the development of Narmada, which includes the construction of a special path around the river for the devotees and a rest house at a distance of every 50-km. Like the BJP, the Congress party also seems to have found a hope in Lord Ram as the manifesto promises the construction of 'Ram Path,' a mythical path taken by Lord Rama during his 14 years long of exile. Congress' Ram Path will stretch from Chitrakoot to the borders of Chhattisgarh.&lt;br /&gt;While promising a corruption-free government, the Congress has promised a Public Accountability Bill for transparency in governance, while there is a lot for farmers in the manifesto including loan waiver up to Rs 2 lakh, reducing electricity bill for agriculture use by 50 per cent, special bonus on production of cereals like wheat, paddy, jowar, maize, soyabean, mustard, and pulses like arhar, moong, channa, masoor; vegetables like onion, garlic, tomato, and crops like sugarcane and cotton. The manifesto also promises Rs 5 per litre bonus on milk besides giving rebate on diesel and petrol to farmers for agricultural use.&lt;br /&gt;The 'Right to Shelter' law will entitle homeless people to Rs 2.5 lakh and 450 sq ft plot for the construction of houses, while the youth and women have been given the lure of 'Made in Madhya Pradesh,' which will focus on increasing employment generation for one lakh youth in the information and technology sector.&lt;br /&gt;"A Vivekanand Yuva Shakti Mission" will be started under which Rs 4,000 per month will be given to youth for participation. To encourage employment and investment Rs 10,000 will be given as salary and grant. Vyapam will be shut down and job recruitment will be made transparent..." states the manifesto.&lt;br /&gt;To promote sports and encourage sportspersons, the Congress has promised jobs to all international players. The players will be provided Rs 50,000 as honorarium in case they are not given jobs. Those players who win gold medals in Olympics will be given Rs 51,000 per month.&lt;br /&gt;Under the 'One man, one pension' scheme, pension amount will be increased to Rs 1,000 from Rs 300, while under the 'Naya Savera' scheme, a rebate of Rs 100 on cooking gas will be provided to poor and labour class people.&lt;br /&gt;For women, the Congress manifesto promises several special schemes which includes free education to girls from school till they complete PhD, smart phones, smartcards and health cards and Rs 51,000 to every young woman who gets married. Women in rural areas will be provided with sewing machines and will be trained to be self-reliant.  (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/mp-bjp-mla-equates-congress-with-butchers-for-promising-gaushala201811111225010001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Rameshwar_Sharma11.jpg</url><title>MP BJP MLA equates Congress with 'butchers' for promising gaushala</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Rameshwar_Sharma11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Cong's MP manifesto promises to ban RSS shakhas in govt buildings</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/congs-mp-manifesto-promises-to-ban-rss-shakhas-in-govt-buildings201811111221570001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Congress_Nov11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhopal (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Ahead of the Madhya Pradesh elections, the Congress party in its manifesto has assured that if voted to power in the state then it will not allow the Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS) to conduct their (shakha) sessions in government buildings.&lt;br /&gt;The party promised to revoke the orders allowing government employees to attend RSS shakha sessions.&lt;br /&gt;Madhya Pradesh is all set to go to polls on November 28. The strength of the Madhya Pradesh assembly is 230 and counting of votes for the assembly elections will be conducted on December 11.&lt;br /&gt;The election in the state is seen as a direct political battle between the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) and the Congress. While Madhya Pradesh Chief Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan is attempting to secure a fourth consecutive term, the Congress will fight for regaining power after 2003.&lt;br /&gt;The Congress on Saturday promised 'Gaushalas,' 'Ram Path' and Naramada Parikrama Path and a spiritual centre to woo voters to its fold in the state. The manifesto also promised to ban alcohol in the state.&lt;br /&gt;In an attempt to outsmart the BJP, the Congress manifesto known as 'Vachan Patra' or 'Sheet of promises,' focuses on, among other things, the issues which have not only been close to its rival BJP's heart but have also been giving political sustenance to the saffron outfit for long. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/congs-mp-manifesto-promises-to-ban-rss-shakhas-in-govt-buildings201811111221570001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Congress_Nov11.jpg</url><title>Cong's MP manifesto promises to ban RSS shakhas in govt buildings</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Congress_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>National permit vehicles can now ply without two drivers</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/national-permit-vehicles-can-now-ply-without-two-drivers201811111057000001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_2018Nov11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Delhi [India], Nov 11 (ANI): The Ministry of Road, Transport and Highways has announced that the national permit vehicles can now ply without two drivers.&lt;br /&gt;Besides that, for national permit vehicles the requirements of having a dark brown body colour and having two drivers have been done away with.&lt;br /&gt;"The words 'National Permit or N/P' shall be inscribed in the front and rear of the vehicles in bold letters. In the case of trailers, the words 'N/P' shall be inscribed on the rear and left side of the vehicle. The body of a tanker carrying dangerous or hazardous goods shall be painted in white colour and shall display the class label," read a statement from the ministry.&lt;br /&gt;Furthermore, making amendments in rule 62 of the Central Motor Vehicle Rules (CMVR), the ministry further stated that from now onward the renewal of fitness in respect of transport vehicles will be every two years for vehicles up to eight years old and one year for vehicles older than eight years.&lt;br /&gt;The renewal of fitness was every year earlier. "No fitness certification shall be required at the time of registration for new transport vehicle sold as fully built vehicle and such vehicle shall be deemed to be having a certificate of fitness for a period of two years from the date of registration. These measures would ease the transport sector of the regulatory requirements and would help to reduce corruption and increase the efficiency of the sector," the statement read.&lt;br /&gt;Under rule 138B, now the goods carriage vehicles cannot carry goods openly, the ministry stated. "They can carry in the closed body or within covers like tarpaulin, etc. This was a cause of nuisance when vehicles carrying say construction material, garbage, etc were moving without covers," the statement added.&lt;br /&gt;It further stated that the production of documents like registration, insurance, fitness, permit and driving licence to the enforcement authorities on their asking can now under the CMVR be in electronic form also, under rule 139.&lt;br /&gt;"This will be very beneficial for a common citizen in this age of mobiles and IT. The citizens are now not required to carry documents in physical form while driving. Although under the IT Act 2000 the document in electronic form was prescribed, enforcement authorities were still pressing for physical documents as per CMVR," the ministry said. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/national-permit-vehicles-can-now-ply-without-two-drivers201811111057000001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_2018Nov11.jpg</url><title>National permit vehicles can now ply without two drivers</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_2018Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>C'garh: Naxal killed in Bijapur encounter</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/cgarh-naxal-killed-in-bijapur-encounter201811111048110001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naxal_Oct%2012.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bijapur (Chhattisgarh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): A Naxal was killed and another was apprehended in an encounter between security forces and Maoists in Bijapur district's Bedre area of Chhattisgarh on Sunday. The operation is still underway.&lt;br /&gt;Arms and ammunition were recovered from the site. Further details are awaited.&lt;br /&gt;In another incident, a Border Security Force (BSF) Assistant Sub-inspector (ASI) was injured in an Improvised Explosive Device (IED) blast in Kanker's Koyalibeda area today morning.&lt;br /&gt;ASI Mahender Singh sustained splinter and bullet injury on his neck. A set of six IEDs were planted in a series and were set off in one go between village Gome and Gattakal in Koyalibeda.&lt;br /&gt;On November 8, at least four civilians and one Central Industrial Security Force (CISF) personnel were killed after Naxals triggered a blast in a bus near Bacheli in Dantewada district.&lt;br /&gt;As many as 18 assembly seats in eight districts of Chhattisgarh will go to polls tomorrow (November 12). The polling for remaining 72 seats will take place on November 20 and the counting of votes will take place on December 11.&lt;br /&gt;Tight security arrangements are in place in the Naxal-affected areas of the state to ensure that no untoward incident occurs during the polling process. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/cgarh-naxal-killed-in-bijapur-encounter201811111048110001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naxal_Oct%2012.jpg</url><title>C'garh: Naxal killed in Bijapur encounter</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Naxal_Oct%2012.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Delhi air quality improves slightly but still in 'very poor' category</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/delhi-air-quality-improves-slightly-but-still-in-very-poor-category201811111045060001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_Nov11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Delhi [India], Nov 11 (ANI): The air quality in the national capital improved slightly on Sunday, bringing down pollution levels from 'hazardous' to 'very poor', even as a thick blanket of smog and haze continued to envelop the region.&lt;br /&gt;The pollution monitoring agencies stated that the extra load of pollutants generated from crop residue burning from neighbouring states such as Punjab and Haryana has also registered a slight drop, leading to slight improvement in the air quality.&lt;br /&gt;The Air Quality Index (AQI) in Delhi improved from 440 on Saturday to 339 today, said centre-run System of Air Quality and Weather Forecasting and Research (SAFAR). "The level may not improve further as weather conditions are still unfavourable," it added.&lt;br /&gt;Notably, an AQI between the range of 0-50 is considered good, the range between 51 to 100 is marked as satisfactory and 101-200 is moderate, 201-300 comes under the category of poor and 401 -500 severe and beyond 500 is contemplated as hazardous.&lt;br /&gt;At Dhirpur, the AQI was 307 at 9:30 am, while in Mathura Road area it dipped to 347 categories at 'very poor'. Furthermore, AQI near Pitampura, Airport Terminal 3 and Delhi University stood at 297, 320 and 289 respectively.&lt;br /&gt;Contamination of atmosphere has become a major concern of new civilized world, which has a serious toxicological impact on not only on adults but also children. People residing in Delhi and National Capital Region, are worried for their children's well being as schools will be reopened tomorrow despite smog and surging pollution.&lt;br /&gt;Speaking to ANI, Roopali Jain, a mother of two children said, "There are no air purifiers in the classrooms and there I can't think of any other way to provide fresh air to my children. School holidays should be extended for the next few days until the air quality improves."&lt;br /&gt;As per the Environment Pollution Control Authority (EPCA), under Graded Response Action Plan (GRAP), the task force will take a call on whether to keep the schools shut or not.&lt;br /&gt;The medical practitioners across the city have advised people suffering from breathing difficulties to avoid outside activities as it may exacerbate their respiratory diseases. They have recommended people to use mask whenever they step out of their houses.&lt;br /&gt;Taking the cognisance of the prevailing situation, the EPCA has extended the ban on construction activities, industries using biomass and coal till November 12. Not only that, the entry of heavy vehicles such as trucks in the capital has also been restricted.&lt;br /&gt;It was also agreed that during this period New Delhi Municipal Council (NDMC) will ensure that wastes are being physically removed and taken to a disposable site so that it can be incinerated properly.&lt;br /&gt;It has been found out that the 12000 tons of industrial and plastic waste have been removed till November 5 since EPCA directed NDMC to remove the waste lying on the roadside on October 27. However remaining industrial wastage also needs to be removed.&lt;br /&gt;EPCA has also asked to file a compliance report at the earliest on steps are taken to ensure that there are systematic collection and transportation of waste material on regular basis.(ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/delhi-air-quality-improves-slightly-but-still-in-very-poor-category201811111045060001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_Nov11.jpg</url><title>Delhi air quality improves slightly but still in 'very poor' category</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Delhi_Nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>TN fishermen warned against venturing into south-east Bay of Bengal</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/tn-fishermen-warned-against-venturing-into-south-east-bay-of-bengal201811111041310001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/IMD_11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chennai (Tamil Nadu) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Tamil Nadu fisheries department has urged the fishermen to avoid fishing in the south-east of the Bay of Bengal tomorrow due to a prediction of stormy weather.&lt;br /&gt;India Meteorological Department (IMD) issued a warning stating that a cyclonic storm can be expected in next 12 hours.&lt;br /&gt;"The deep depression over southeast and adjoining central Bay of Bengal moved west-northwestwards and lay centered at night of 10th November, at about 1120 km east-southeast of Nellore (Andhra Pradesh). It is very likely to intensify into a cyclonic storm during next 12 hours," stated IMD.&lt;br /&gt;Fishermen in Andhra Pradesh have also been warned against venturing into the sea for the next 24 hours as the conditions are expected to deteriorate and get rough along and off south-Andhra Pradesh coast from November 13 evening.&lt;br /&gt;Fishermen who are in the deep sea have been advised to return to coast before November 12. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/tn-fishermen-warned-against-venturing-into-south-east-bay-of-bengal201811111041310001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/IMD_11.jpg</url><title>TN fishermen warned against venturing into south-east Bay of Bengal</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/IMD_11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>PM Modi to dedicate two highways to Varanasi on Monday</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/pm-modi-to-dedicate-two-highways-to-varanasi-on-monday201811110745520001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Modi_Nov7.jpg" alt="PM Modi" title="PM Modi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Varanasi (Uttar Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Prime Minister Narendra Modi will dedicate two important national highways in Uttar Pradesh's Varanasi on November 12.&lt;br /&gt;The total length of the highways is 34 kilometres and is constructed at a cost of over Rs 1,500 crore.&lt;br /&gt;The two projects will reduce travel time in the area and will also provide easier and more convenient access to Sarnath, which is an important site for Buddhist pilgrimage.&lt;br /&gt;The Prime Minister will also dedicate an inland waterways terminal to the nation on river Ganga in Varanasi.&lt;br /&gt;This will be the first of the four multi-modal terminals on River Ganga, which is a part of the World Bank-aided Jal Marg Vikas project of the Inland Waterways Authority of India.&lt;br /&gt;The multimodal terminals aim to develop the stretch of River Ganga between Varanasi to Haldi for navigation of large vessels up to 1500-2000 tonnes weight, with an objective to promote inland waterways as a cheaper and more environment-friendly means of transport.&lt;br /&gt;The estimated cost of this project is Rs 5,369.18 crores on a 50:50 sharing basis between the Indian government and the World Bank.&lt;br /&gt;Apart from this, he will also receive India's First Container Cargo being transported on an Inland Waterway.&lt;br /&gt;Operation, management and further development of the multimodal terminal is proposed to be entrusted to an operator on Public-private partnership (PPP) model. Selection of the PPP operator through an International Competitive Bidding is at an advanced stage and expected to be completed by December 2018.&lt;br /&gt;Prime Minister will also receive India's first container vessel that sailed from Kolkata, carrying cargo of PEPSICO (India).&lt;br /&gt;The Inland Waterways Authority of India (IWAI) vessel, MV Rabindranath Tagore is transporting 16 containers and it will make its return journey with fertilizers from IFFCO. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/pm-modi-to-dedicate-two-highways-to-varanasi-on-monday201811110745520001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Modi_Nov7.jpg</url><title>PM Modi to dedicate two highways to Varanasi on Monday</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/Modi_Nov7.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Janardhan Reddy questioned for hours in bribery case</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/janardhan-reddy-questioned-for-hours-in-bribery-case201811110739410001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/reddy_nov11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bengaluru (Karnataka) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Former Minister and mining baron Janardhan Reddy on Saturday reached the Central Crime Branch (CCB) office for questioning in connection with an alleged bribery case.&lt;br /&gt;Around 11 pm, the police had said the questioning is still going on.&lt;br /&gt;"Questioning of Janardhan Reddy is on. At appropriate time, appropriate decision will be taken as per provisions of law," Alok Kumar, additional commissioner of police (crime), said.&lt;br /&gt;Reddy is suspected to have received 57 kg of gold worth Rs 18 crore to help an accused in a case being investigated by the Enforcement Directorate (ED). Along with Reddy, his secretary Ali, jeweller Ramesh Kothari and one other have been named as accomplices in the alleged fraud case.&lt;br /&gt;Earlier, Karnataka commissioner of police, T Suneel Kumar had said, "A company Ambidant, set up in 2016-17 assured investors a return of 30-40 per cent per month in form of profits. Thousands of people were lured to invest. Initially, they returned the first batch profits as promised following which more people poured in. Subsequently, when it failed to return the principal amount, cases were registered. In January 2017, the ED raided the company. The crime branch took over the case and a probe was conducted which revealed that transactions to the tune of Rs. 18 crore were carried out."&lt;br /&gt;Later, it was discovered that the company had allegedly transferred the money to Ramesh Kothari who runs a billion business in the name of Ambika Jewellers. On quizzing Kothari, he informed that he had used the money to buy the gold, which was handed over to Reddy's personal assistant Ali. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/janardhan-reddy-questioned-for-hours-in-bribery-case201811110739410001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/reddy_nov11.jpg</url><title>Janardhan Reddy questioned for hours in bribery case</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/reddy_nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>MP polls: FIR against BJP candidate for organising rally without permission</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/mp-polls-fir-against-bjp-candidate-for-organising-rally-without-permission201811110725390001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/bjplogojan26.jpg" alt="Representative image" title="Representative image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narsinghpur (Madhya Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI): An FIR has been lodged against Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) candidate from Gadarwara constituency for organising rally without permission from the administration.&lt;br /&gt;BJP's Gautam Patel and his associates organised the rally in the constituency without permission on November 8.&lt;br /&gt;Section 144 of the Criminal Procedure Code (CrPC), 1973, which prohibits an assembly of more than four persons in an area, was imposed in the constituency from October 6.&lt;br /&gt;The state is slated to go to polls on November 28. The strength of the Madhya Pradesh assembly is 230 and counting of votes for the assembly elections will be conducted on December 11.&lt;br /&gt;The election in the state is seen as a direct political battle between the BJP and the Congress. While Madhya Pradesh Chief Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan is attempting to secure a fourth consecutive term, the Congress will fight for regaining power after 2003. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/mp-polls-fir-against-bjp-candidate-for-organising-rally-without-permission201811110725390001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/bjplogojan26.jpg</url><title>MP polls: FIR against BJP candidate for organising rally without permission</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/bjplogojan26.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Petrol, diesel prices continue to fall on Sunday</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/petrol-diesel-prices-continue-to-fall-on-sunday201811110712180001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/fuelprices_nov11.jpg" alt="Representative Image" title="Representative Image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Delhi [India], Nov 11 (ANI): Petrol and Diesel prices continued to witness a decline in the national capital on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;Petrol price in New Delhi saw a dip of 16 paise and is now being retailed at Rs 77.73 per litre, while diesel price was decreased by 12 paise and is now being sold at Rs 72.46 per litre.&lt;br /&gt;Meanwhile, petrol prices in Mumbai also saw a fall of 16 paise to be sold at Rs 83.24 per litre. A litre of diesel is being sold at Rs 75.92 in the financial capital of the country following a dip of 13 paise.&lt;br /&gt;Fuel prices had earlier witnessed a relentless hike in the country, burning holes in commuters' pockets.&lt;br /&gt;In this regard, Union Finance Minister Arun Jaitley had, on October 4, announced a reduction of Rs 2.50 per litre on both petrol and diesel prices after curbing excise duty on the commodity by Rs 1.50 per litre. He had also urged state governments to slash the same amount at their end. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/petrol-diesel-prices-continue-to-fall-on-sunday201811110712180001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/fuelprices_nov11.jpg</url><title>Petrol, diesel prices continue to fall on Sunday</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/fuelprices_nov11.jpg</link></image></item><item><title>Anti-BJP parties likely to meet in Delhi on Nov 22</title><link>https://www.aninews.in/news/anti-bjp-parties-likely-to-meet-in-delhi-on-nov-22201811110706070001/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/chandrababunaidu_nov11.jpg" alt="Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister Chandrababu Naidu" title="Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister Chandrababu Naidu"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amaravati (Andhra Pradesh) [India], Nov 11 (ANI):  All the non-BJP parties are likely to meet on November 22 to decide on future course of action under a slogan of save democracy and save the nation.&lt;br /&gt;As part of the anti-BJP campaign, Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister N. Chandrababu Naidu on Saturday met Congress party national general secretary and former Rajasthan chief minister Ashok Gehlot at his residence and discussed the future course of action.&lt;br /&gt;Naidu said that efforts are on to bring together all non-BJP parties and that he had met Congress president Rahul Gandhi to discuss measures on protecting democracy.&lt;br /&gt;Taking a dig at Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Naidu said that the former is responsible for the present state of affairs in Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) and Reserve Bank of India (RBI).&lt;br /&gt;"The country's economy is in doldrums with the interfering of the central government on regulating authorities like CBI and RBI. RBI is a regulating authority and independently regulate the economy," he said while adding that the BJP government has been resorting to IT raids on opposition leaders for political gains.&lt;br /&gt;Referring to Demonetisation, Naidu said that even after two years there is no result. The BJP government claimed that demonetisation would help to bring the black money back but it turned as a futile exercise, he added.&lt;br /&gt;"Country's economy is in the doldrums. There was a fall in rupee value, increase in prices of essential commodities, unemployment increased, intolerance among SC, STs and minorities, secular fabric damaged and unrest prevailed in the country. The central government is resorting to conduct raids on those questioning including media, politicians to frighten them," the Chief Minister said.&lt;br /&gt;Speaking on the occasion, Ashok Gehlot said that Naidu met Rahul Gandhi and discussed how to save democracy. He underlined that no one is happy with Prime Minister Narendra Modi-led government including farmers, youth, women, poor and petty traders.&lt;br /&gt;Gehlot said that the BJP government claimed to utilise demonetisation to end terrorism but failed.&lt;br /&gt;The Centre has been destroying Judiciary, CBI, Election Commission, IT for the first time after independence. The present situation is an undeclared emergency in the country, Gehlot added.&lt;br /&gt;It is a time for an important role to play. We will gather all together on November 22 to finalise the future course of action. We will move forward with Rahul Gandhi's agenda, he added.&lt;br /&gt;To establish Anti-BJP platform, Naidu till date has met Congress party president Rahul Gandhi, National Congress (NC) chief Farooq Abdullah, Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP) supremo Mayawati, Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal, veteran leader Sharad Yadav, former BJP leader Yashwant Sinha,  Samjadwati party leaders Mulayam Singh and Akhilesh Yadav.&lt;br /&gt;The Chief Minister said that it is time to take a decision on the country's future.&lt;br /&gt;"I have no personal interest. We have to protect the country, democracy', constitutional rights should be protected.  We are strong in technology, Youths are more. Narendra Modi's negative attitude and unilateral decisions along with Amit Shah leading to problems in the country. The Modi-Shah duo is destroying the systems in the country and giving priority to their own man," he said.&lt;br /&gt;The Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister has been extremely vocal and straight-forward about his critical opinions against the Centre. He had earlier said that the country needs a national-level alliance to counter Prime Minister Narendra Modi-led National Democratic Alliance (NDA) in the upcoming 2019 Lok Sabha elections. (ANI)&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">ANI</dc:creator><guid>https://www.aninews.in/news/anti-bjp-parties-likely-to-meet-in-delhi-on-nov-22201811110706070001/</guid><category>National</category><category>General News</category><image><url>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/chandrababunaidu_nov11.jpg</url><title>Anti-BJP parties likely to meet in Delhi on Nov 22</title><link>https://aniportalimages.s3.amazonaws.com/media/details/chandrababunaidu_nov11.jpg</link></image></item></channel></rss>